Finding Aid for the Marvin A. Kahn papers LSC.2436
UCLA Library Special Collections
Marvin A. Kahn papers
1946-2016
UCLA Library Special Collections
Kahn, Marvin Aaron
Kahn, Ava F.
LSC.2436
3.8 linear feet (3 flat boxes)
This collection documents apartment buildings in Westwood, along with social and professional activities of the contractor and property manager, Marvin Aaron Kahn.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Ava F. Kahn, 2018.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9996940136506533
Biographical History
Marvin Aaron Kahn was a contractor and founded the property management company Westwood Property Management. Kahn earned his MA in Education from UCLA. Kahn also served as president of the Westwood Chamber of Commerce.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains 12 original watercolor paintings of apartments in Westwood Village built between 1946-1969. Most of these buildings were built as student housing and were managed by Westwood Property Management; Marvin Kahn's property management company. The collection also contains a scrapbook documenting business activity in Westwood and ephemera documenting Kahn's professional and personal activities.
Apartments -- California -- Westwood; Student housing -- California -- Westwood; Real estate management -- California -- Westwood; Kahn, Ava F.; Kahn, Marvin Aaron -- Archives
- Watercolor paintings of Westwood buildings
  - 2316 Cotner, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 2033 Pontius, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1001 Gayley, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 400 Gayley, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 919 Levering, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 885 Levering, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 901 Levering, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 801-803, 815-817 Levering, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 641 Landfair, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 555 Kelton, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 16525 Sunset Blvd., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 625 Landfair, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Photograph of Marvin Kahn, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Certificates, 1975-2016 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Scrapbook, 1948-1971 (Box 3)